Résumé

Introduction

My name is Abdul-Qudus Olajide, and I'm a 'Tech Dude' with penchant for Web Programing, Software Development, Interactive designs and UI/UX.

In 2019, I graduated from the University of Lagos, with a degree in Mathematics and Statistics. I joined an eCommerce company shortly after as a Front-End Developer.

While at the University I served as the Team Lead of the branding department at AIESEC, amongst other Leadership positions attained thereof.

Contact

Email: jideabdqudus@gmail.com

Phone: +2348092399019

Web: abdulqudus.com Instagram: @theQoder

Education

Bsc Mathematics/Statistics
University of Lagos, Nigeria.
September 2015 - September 2019.

Skills

FrontEnd - HTML5, (S)CSS, Bootstrap4, ReactJS
Backend - JS(Node), REST, Mongo, Laravel.

Design - Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma.

Others - Design thinking, Mathematics, Git

Languages

English, Yoruba,

Experience

Paysmosmo (Nov 2019 - Present)

Paysmosmo is an eCommerce company with focus on Credit sales.

Coinlinks (Feb 2020 - Apr 2020)

Coinlinks is an eCommerce company based in Florida, USA with focus on Cryptocurrency as medium of exchange. I worked remotely as a Software developer and UI/UX composer.

TechEnd (Oct 2018 - Feb 2019)

TechEnd is a Software development company and I Interned as a Web Developer, playing a major role in website development, API authorization, web routing thereof.

Personal Projects

- Built a payment platform using Vanilla JS and MaterializeCSS for an ALC project with GraphQL deployed on a MongoDB and Node instance. (2019)
- Postify, a social web app, poised to look and operate like Twitter. Built using React JS and Redux for state management. (2020)
- Co-built a Business Directory platform called Hire-Me that connects small scale business owners to interested customers, the application serves as a Yellow Page. (2020)

Leadership & Community Roles

- AIESEC Lagos, Executive Team Leader, Branding.
- Andela Learning Community (ALC), Trainee.
- Young African Leaders Initititave (YALI), Alumni.
- Code Lagos, Trainee.